{
  "shortDescription": "Challenge your knowledge of Phaver!",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is Phaver?",
      "answers": ["Social Media", "Game", "DEX"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which protocol Phaver allows crossposting on?",
      "answers": ["Lens", "Farcaster", "Both"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "How many Levels are there on Phaver?",
      "answers": ["Two", "Four", "Five"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "To level up on Phaver, what do you need?",
      "answers": ["Creds", "Points", "Phaves"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "How many creds do you need for L2?",
      "answers": ["10", "100", "250"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Creds reset in how many days?",
      "answers": ["10", "30", "20"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "1000 creds in 30 days will get you which level?",
      "answers": ["L2", "L4", "L5"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Posting on Phaver earns you?",
      "answers": ["Creds", "Tokens", "Points"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "How many points are charged for Super Post?",
      "answers": ["50", "500", "0"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How many points are charged for Premium Post?",
      "answers": ["10", "50", "100"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Creds can be earned by?",
      "answers": ["NFTs", "Badges", "Both"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of official NFT project on Phaver?",
      "answers": ["Phaver UP", "Phaverite", "PhavNFT"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Phaver season 1 airdrop is called?",
      "answers": ["Airdrop", "Phairdrop", "Phavair"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you post on farcaster directly from Phaver?",
      "answers": ["Yes", "No", "Maybe"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "How many daily phaves L2 gets?",
      "answers": ["5", "10", "20"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "How many daily phaves L4 gets?",
      "answers": ["10", "20", "40"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Staking your phaves early on a super or premium post earns you?",
      "answers": ["Points", "Creds", "Both"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "L5 gets 40 phaves daily?",
      "answers": ["Yes", "No", "No idea"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "How many creds do you need for L5?",
      "answers": ["250", "1000", "3000"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "How many creds Phaver UP NFT earn daily?",
      "answers": ["20", "35", "50"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    }
  ]
}